

John Gilbert

System Engineer (TCS)

My Contact

johngilbert.kochery@gmail.com

(L) 8129217563

Kochery(H),Mundamveli, Ernakulam,Kreala

https://www.linkedin.com/in/johngilbert-9660a7172/

Hard Skill

- Automation Testing With Selenium
- Programming in Java,C,C++,HTML,CSS
- PI/SQIL, My SQL

Soft Skill

- Observation
- · Decision making
- Communication
- Team Work

Education Background

- Rajagiri College of Social Sciences (Master of Computer Applications) in Progress
- St. Alberts College, Autonomous (Bsc. Computer Science)
 Completed in 2019

About Me

I am a dedicated and detail-oriented Automation Test Engineer with 3 years of experience. Eager to work with an organization where i can implement my knowledge and improve my skills to become a better professional and thereby improve the company profit.

Professional Experience

Tata Consultancy Services | System Engineer 2019 - 2022

Key responsibilities:

- Identify the Test Cases
- Test the story till E2E environment.
- Run the Automation script in a regular base.
- Report the Environment issue.

Nielsen India Pvt Ltd | Translation

2016 - 2019 (part time job)

Key responsibilities:

- To translate the respondent comments to English.
- · Record all the hand written work into system.
- Call the respondent for a final verification.

Achievements

2021 - 2022 National Wushu Player

2015–Present Taking Classes for Fitness and Martial

Arts in Ernakulam,Kerala